>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 让我们开始练习函数表达式。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So let's jump into
our exercise on function expressions.
为函数表达式练习向上拉自述文件和 ex.js 。
Pull up the readme and the ex.js for
the function expressions exercise.
在这次演习中
In this exercise,
你会写一些函数和函数表达式
you're gonna be writing some functions and
also some function expressions.
这些功能将管理一些学生的注册记录
And these functions are gonna be managing
some student enrollment records for
我们的工作室
our workshop.
运动的精神是你将利用我们所学到的
The spirit of the exercise is that you're
gonna be using what we've learned about
指定函数并尽可能使用函数。
named functions and
using functions wherever possible.
所以你想用地图和过滤器之类的东西
So you wanna be using things like map and
filter and
而不是你的旧学校
find instead of your old school for loops.
你想尽可能地使用功能。
You wanna use functions wherever possible.
这一运动分为两部分。
This is broken up into two parts,
this exercise.
首先，完成第一部分，然后完成第二部分。
First, complete part one and
then complete part two.
回来，回来的时候我们都解释解
We'll come back, when we come back we
will explain the solution for both so
你就有时间在这两处工作了
you will have time to work on both parts.
第一部分，你要做的是写函数声明和命名函数
In part one, what you're gonna do is write
a function declarations and named function
根据此处的指示信息，我将在此时结束这些表达式。
expressions according to the instructions
here, and I'll go over those in a moment.
第二部分你要做的就是重写
In part two,
what you're going to do is rewrite
所有您作为箭头函数执行的函数。
all of those functions that
you did as arrow functions.
第一部分和第二部分用于
The purpose of part one and
part two is for
您可以并排比较代码可读性和
you to have a side by side comparison of
the differences in code readability and
使用命名函数和使用箭头函数之间的功能，好吗 ?
functionality between using named
functions and using arrow functions, okay?
所以在行为上不会有任何区别
So there won't be any
difference in behavior,
只是这两部分之间的代码风格的不同
just simply a difference in code
style between those two parts.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 您需要实施的主要功能是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The main functionality
that you need to implement is that
有三个功能叫做 printRecords
there are three functions,
called printRecords,
paidStudentsToEnroll ，并保留，对不起，reminidUnp酬。
paidStudentsToEnroll, and
remain, I'm sorry, remindUnpaid.
这三个函数已在 ex.js 文件中进行了存根。
Those three functions have been
stubbed out in the ex.js file.
他们是来找你的你知道他们的论点是什么
They're there for you, you see what
they receive as arguments, I mean,
作为参数。
as parameters.
但您需要根据自述文件的内容实施这些操作。
But you need to implement those
according to what the readme says.
你会注意到那些功能已经给你打电话了
And you'll notice that those functions
are already called for you, so
我给打印记录打了电话
here I've called printRecords.
我调用 paidStudentsToEnroll ，我调用remindUnp酬和
I call paidStudentsToEnroll and
I call remindUnpaid and
此代码注释中期望的输出。
the output that is expected
is here in this code comment.
因此，您的输出需要与此输出相匹配，好吗 ?
So your output needs to match this output,
okay?
打印记录执行的操作是获取学生标识列表。
What printRecords does is it
takes a list of student IDs.
就像你在这里看到的一样
So it's gonna take an array of
student IDs as you see here,
我们正在传递一个名为 " currentEnrollment" 的学生标识的数组。
we are passing in an array of student
IDs called currentEnrollment.
所以打印记录列出了学生标识和
So printRecords takes
a list of student IDs and
需要检索每个学生的记录。
needs to retrieve each student record.
这些存储在 studentRecords 数组中。
Those are stored in
the studentRecords array.
按标识检索每个记录，并且您可以使用数组查找。
Retrieve each record by ID, and there's
a hint there than you can use array find.
按学生姓名升序排序。
Sorted by the student name, ascending.
您可以使用数组排序，但必须使用定制功能。
You can use array sort, but you're
gonna have to use a custom function.
然后将每个记录打印到控制台或控制台日志语句，包括
And then print each record to the console
or the console log statement including
他们的名字，他们的身份，以及他们是否得到支付。
their name, their ID, and
whether or not they're paid.
这就是这个功能的作用。
That's what that function does.
2 号，有报酬的注册学生都看透了学生
Number two, the paid students to enroll
function looks through all the student
记录并检查是否有任何已支付但尚未注册的情况。
records and checks to see if any of
them are paid but not yet enrolled.
意味着它们尚未出现在 currentEnrollment 数组中，
Meaning they're not yet
in the currentEnrollment array,
他们的身份不存在
their ID isn't there.
收集这些标识和
Collect those IDs and
然后返回具有先前注册的标识加上新标识的新阵列。
then return a new array with the
previously enrolled IDs plus the new ones.
因此，它不会修改，它会返回一个新的数组。
So, it doesn't modify,
it returns a new array.
最后，你将会收到一份学生身份证的清单
And finally, the remindUnpaid is you're
gonna take a list of student IDs and
将该列表过滤为仅记录处于未支付状态的记录。
filter that list to only ones whose
records are in the unpaid status.
然后将该列表从项目 1 传递回我们的打印记录
And then pass that list back to
our printRecords from item one
只打印出不带薪的学生
to print out only
the students that are unpaid.
好的，所以这是第二次运动的一部分，第二部分，
Okay, so this is part one of
the exercise and again, part two,
你不会改变任何行为，只要用箭头函数重新编写它。
you don't change any behavior, you just
simply rewrite it with arrow functions.
一般来说，第一部分应该带您大约 15 分钟，
Generally speaking, part one should
take you about 15 minutes and
第二部分应该带你五分钟
part two should take
you about five minutes.
因此，我们会在约 20 分钟内完成这项工作。
So overall we would take about
20 minutes to do this exercise.
因此，我们现在就休息，让你有机会练习第一部分和第二部分。
So we'll break now, let you have a chance
to work on exercise part one and part two.
我建议将您的解决方案放在两个单独的文件中
I'd recommend putting your
solutions in two separate files so
你可以对比和对比
that you can compare and contrast them.
我们很快就会回来，通过这个方案来谈谈。
We'll come back in a little bit and talk
through the solution to this exercise.
提醒你如果你被困住了你需要一点点的手
Reminder that if you get stuck and you
need a little bit of a hand through you
与进行欺骗一样，解决方案文件在 EXfix-1 和 EXfix-2中。
just like to cheat, the solutions files
are there in EXfix-1 and EXfix-2.